jegsworks.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy | Jegsworks

* * *

**What information do we collect?**

The site does not require a login so we don't require personal data. We do collect web site usage data as part of the process of sending you a web page to view, just like any other web site. We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, or fill out a form. 

**Web site usage data:** Your computer automatically sends technical information to our hosting computer in order for our web pages to display on your computer. This is true for all web sites. Some of the data can be used to make sure the web page will display correctly in your browser. We also analyze the usage data to help improve the site and correct errors.

We collect:

  * IP address of your device as well as your internet service provider (ISP)
  * Referring page: If you clicked on a link to get to a page on the site, the URL of that referring page
  * Date and time of the visit and the duration of use of the site
  * What pages you viewed during the visit and which one you were on when you exited the site
  * Information about your device - type of device, browser type and version, operating system.

**Submitting a form:** When requesting permission to use the site with a class or submitting an evaluation, you complete a form that asks for your name, email address, and information about the class. The only personal information is your name and email address. This information will be kept on the server that processes the forms at FormToEmail.com and in our office in a spreadsheet and in emails that contain what you submitted.

**Ordering:** When ordering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information. 

**Cookies:** Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/) .

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To display a web page on your computer

> Your computer or device sends technical data to the hosting computer in order to display web pages. This process collects the IP address of your computer, your ISP, information about your computer including the operating system, browser version, and type of device, and the date and time of your visit, what pages your view, how long you are on the site, what page you exit the site from.

To analyze visitor traffic to improve the site

> We look at the site's statistics to see what parts of the most used and least used to help us improve the site. We look for broken links.

To process transactions 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails  

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. You may sign up for our email notifications also. 

To respond to comments

> We may respond by email to comments that you include in your form submissions. We may verify that your requested permission to use the web site materials in a class or that you ordered products.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order through a third-party order processing service.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After _**a transaction**_ , your private information (credit cards, name, email address, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

Information submitted by form will be kept indefinitely, but will never be sold or shared except as needed to process your orders or support needs.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, as part of Google ads. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We also use cookies as part of the site's expanding menus. There is no personal information recorded by these cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 05/16/2018.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.jegsworks.com

Jan Smith  
jegs1@jegsworks.com

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to [Zendesk](http://www.rhinosupport.com/zendesk.htm) and save!
